In the next part of the lesson,
在课程的下一部分
you'll be working on the extract part of an ETL pipeline.
你将处理 ETL 管道的数据提取部分
You will be extracting data from different sources like CSV files,
你将从不同的数据源 如 CSV 文件 JSON文件
JSON files, XML, and SQL databases.
XML 和 SQL 数据库提取数据
I'm just going to give you a brief overview about how
我会简单介绍一下
this section is organized and what you can expect?
本章的内容结构和你将要学习的知识
You'll notice in general,
你会注意到 大致上
this lesson isn't too heavy on theory,
本课程并不注重理论
it's mostly practical exercises so that you gain practice moving,
大多数都是实践性的练习 这样你可以练习移动
cleaning, and preparing data.
清洗和准备数据等技能
You'll see that whenever there's an exercise,
有练习的地方
it's marked here on the left as an exercise.
会在左侧标记为练习
All of the exercises are contained in Jupyter Notebooks.
所有的练习包含在 Jupyter notebook 里
When you open an exercise,
当你打开一个练习
the notebook opens automatically in the workspace.
工作环境中会自动打开一个 notebook
To complete the exercise,
要完成练习
read through the notebooks and follow the instructions.
你需要阅读 notebook 并按照要求完成
For some code cells,
对于某些代码单元格
you only need to run them,
你只需要运行它们
but for other code cells,
但对于另一些代码单元格
there's going to be a to do with instructions.
包含一些带有要求的待办事项/任务（TODO）
So, whenever you see a to do,
所以 当你看到 TODO 的时候
that means you have some code to write.
说明你需要写一些代码
I want to call your attention to the fact that,
同时 注意
all of these exercises also have solutions.
所有的练习都配有答案
If you click on the Jupyter icon up here,
如果你点击上方的 Jupyter 图标
and then you find the file with the exercise you're currently working on,
然后你会找到你正在完成的练习文件
which in this case is one CSV exercise.
这里是一个 CSV 练习
Then click and go inside,
然后点击进入
you can click here,
你点击这里
and open a solution file.
然后打开一个答案文件
So, going back one level,
向上一级
all of these files have the exercises in them in Jupyter Notebooks,
所有这些文件都有 Jupyter Notebooks 形式的练习
and they also have all of the solutions.
并配有全套的答案
Going here to this exercise on JSON, and XML,
进入这里 是 JSON 和 XML 练习
you'll see at the bottom that I've marked a section as a challenge, way down here.
你会看到这下面标注为挑战的一节 一直往下
So, what I mean by that,
这个标注的意思是
is that this part is more challenging and
这一部分更具挑战性
also time-consuming than other parts of the exercise.
比其他部分的练习更费时间
I always put them as the very last thing at the bottom of an exercise.
我把它们放在最后 练习的最底下
If I've marked something as a challenge,
如果标记为挑战
it means, I think you'll get something out of solving it,
说明 我认为你在解决它的过程中会学到新东西
but it's not essential for understanding the lesson material or for
但这些新知识对于理解课程材料或者
getting through the final project at the end of this course.
通关课程的最终项目不是必须的
So, start working on this extract section and then when you get down to transform here,
好的 开始完成数据提取部分吧 当你做到数据转换部分的时候
I'll give another overview about that section as well.
我再给你介绍那个部分